[DOG BARKING]
♪♪♪
♪ MET YOU AT THE DIVE BAR TO GO SHOOT SOME POOL ♪
♪ AND MAKE FUN OF THE COWBOYS WITH THE NECK TATTOOS ♪
♪ ASK YOU EASY QUESTIONS ABOUT WORK AND SCHOOL ♪
♪ I'M TRYING TO BE COOL ABOUT IT ♪
♪ FEELIN' LIKE AN ABSOLUTE FOOL ABOUT IT ♪
♪ WISHIN' YOU WERE KIND ENOUGH TO BE CRUEL ABOUT IT ♪
♪ TELLIN' MYSELF I CAN ALWAYS DO WITHOUT IT ♪
♪ KNOWIN' THAT IT PROBABLY ISN'T TRUE ♪
♪ I CAME PREPARED FOR ABSOLUTION, IF YOU'D ONLY ASK ♪
♪ SO I TAKE SOME OFFENSE WHEN YOU SAY, "NO REGRETS" ♪
♪ I REMEMBER IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO PASS YOUR TEST ♪
♪ BUT I'M TRYING TO FORGET ABOUT IT ♪
♪ FEELIN' LIKE I'M BREAKING A SWEAT ABOUT IT ♪
♪ WISHIN' YOU WOULD KINDLY GET OUT OF MY HEAD ABOUT IT ♪
♪ TELLIN' MYSELF ONE DAY I'LL FORGET ABOUT IT ♪
♪ KNOWIN' THAT IT PROBABLY ISN'T TRUE ♪
♪ ONCE, I TOOK YOUR MEDICATION TO KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE ♪
♪ AND NOW I HAVE TO ACT LIKE I CAN'T READ YOUR MIND ♪
♪ I ASK YOU HOW YOU'RE DOING AND I LET YOU LIE ♪
♪ BUT WE DON'T HAVE TO TALK ABOUT IT ♪
♪ I CAN WALK YOU HOME AND PRACTICE METHOD ACTING ♪
♪ I'LL PRETEND BEING WITH YOU DOESN'T FEEL LIKE DROWNING ♪
♪ TELLIN' YOU IT'S NICE TO SEE HOW GOOD YOU'RE DOING ♪
♪ EVEN THOUGH WE KNOW IT ISN'T TRUE ♪
[CRICKETS]